Lyrics from Genius & Gemini & ChatGPT
Made by Randy
Im sitting in the sunlight of the spirit
我沐浴在精神的阳光中
This life too beautiful to hide what I'm feeling
生命如此美好，不该把感受藏在心底
In the dark, spoke a whisper that God only hearin'
在黑暗中，我轻声说着只有上帝能听见的秘密
This life so beautiful l cry when I feel it
这生命太美好，让我一感受到就忍不住落泪
I cry when l-
忍不住一
Too much of this too much of that
太多的事压在身上
A touch of death a touch of wrath
丝死亡的影子， 丝愤怒的火光
Was in the future, in the past
未来也有，过去也藏
How long it's all gon'last
这一切到底能撑多久？
You won't know if you don't ask
你不问就不会知道
Can't see the wings on your own back
你看不见自己背上的翅膀
Can't fly through a slow track
无法在缓慢的跑道上飞翔
Childhood trauma make you grow fast
童年创伤让你快速成长
Heading home where the sun sets
朝着日落的方向回家
Ilearned that karma is a roadmap
我明自因果报应是一张路线图
All the air that my lungs get
每一次呼吸都提醒我
I say the heart is where the home at
心之所在，即是家之所在
Not the one to pick a bone with
我不会把矛头对向别人
Busy picking apart your own stuff
忙着拆解自己的心事
I wonder how far is closeness
我想知道亲密有多遥远
Won't be dealt pain in doses
我不会再接受那种分批给的伤害
Sunlight of the spirit
精神的阳光酒在我的身上
This life too beautiful to hide what I'm feeling
生命如此美好，不该隐藏我的感受
In the dark, spoke a whisper that God only hearin'
在黑暗中，我轻声细语，只有上帝听得到
This life so beautiful l cry when I feel it
生命如此美好，当我感受它时我会哭泣
Cry when l-
当我 时会哭泣
My only task to learn to grieve
我以前唯一的功课，就是学会好好哀悼
The past will burn a hole in me
过去曾在我心里烧出一个洞
I learned to love the whole of me
我学会了爱完整的自己
And then I found my soul at ease
然后我发现我的灵魂得到了安宁
Safe travels to you, Captain
一路平安，船长（指代逝去的人）
I know you watchin'overme
我知道你在守护着我
Peace, I can only wonder what it all really means
安宁一 我现在只能去猜这一切真正意味着什么
From a boy to a grown man, felt the pen alive in his own hand
从一个男孩到一个成年人，我感受到笔在自己手中有了生命
And it's hard for me to own all the tears I done shed for my old man
我很难承认我为我的父亲流下的所有眼泪
I turned my purpose to the seaside
我将我的目标转向海边
And asked my worry to a slow dance
并邀请我的忧虑跳一支慢舞
You can look me in my two eyes
你只要看进我这双眼
see that Ive only known a lone chance
就会知道我一直以来只有孤身一人的机会
Sunlight of the spirit
精神的阳光
This life too beautiful to hide what I'm feeling
生命如此美好，不该隐藏我的感受
In the dark, spoke a whisper that God only hearin'
在黑暗中，我轻声细语，只有上帝听得到
This life so beautiful l cry when I feel it
生命如此美好，当我感受它时我会哭泣
Im sitting in the sunlight of the spirit
我沐浴在精神的阳光中
This life too beautiful to hide whatI'm feeling
生命如此美好，不该隐藏我的感受
In the dark, spoke a whisper that God only hearin'
在黑暗中，我轻声细语，只有上帝听得到
This life so beautiful l cry when I feel it
生命如此美好，当我感受它时我会哭泣
I could cry when I-
我会哭，我一—